In the not too distant future Next Sunday
AD There was a guy named
Joel not too different from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic Institute Just
another face in a red jumpsuit. He did a
good job cleaning up the place but his
boss didn't like him. Soon they shot him
into space.
We'll send the cheesy movies the
worst we can find. He'll have to
sit and watch them all. Then we'll monitor
his mind. Now, keep in mind,
Joel can't control where the movies begin
or end because he used those
special parts to make his robot friends.
Robot will call Carebot Family Gypsy.
Hi, girl. Tom Servo.
If you're wondering how he eats and
breathes and other science facts,
then repeat to yourself. It's just a show.
I should really relax. For Mystery
Sad Theater 3000.
Hi. Welcome to the Satellite of Love. And
on today's show, we're gonna show you how
to keep those holiday goiters to a
minimum. The secret ordinary table salt.
Then we'll talk to Mom's Mabley, and
she'll tell us how she kept up a good
attitude despite being dead for 20 years.
The circus is in town and I'm going on
location cleaning up after those big bull
elephants. And later, Robert Goulet will
be stopping by and swinging into high,
singing a song and then showing his famous
Bloody Mary mix. I hope he sings the song
first. If you put him. I know, Jerry.
Seconds to commercial sign. And for you
bachelors, we're expecting a Visit from
Wanda McHale and her whale of a tale. So
start your popcorn popping now, boys, and
I'll be on location. A man who ate his
weight in Silly Putty. We'll see it. I bet
he can, you know, take impressions of
newspapers right off his elbow or
something. Anyway, on a sadder note,
Mom's Mabley's AT attitude really isn't
doing all that well. Aw, yeah. Well,
maybe she should try Robert Goulet's
Bloody Mary mix.
All these stories and more not.
So, Joel, what's pain again? Pain is an
intensely uncomfortable feeling, and it's
something you want to stop immediately.
Show me. Yeah. Oh, you're a robot. You
know you can't feel pain. I can't do that.
Come on, Joel, show him. Okay. Pain is
something like this.
Come on, the Mads are calling. Here's some
people that know about pain. Well, these
bandages are ready to come off now,
Frank. Just head off that direction.
Little problem getting the Rosy Greer head
to take. And how about you? Are you ready
for this week's? Invention Exchange.
Katrina. Hmm? Oh, yeah. I've got an
invention exchange this week. If you're
like me, and I know I am, certain days you
come home from school or work and it
suddenly dawns on you, you have a
Halloween party to go to. So I've come up
with some easy Halloween costumes you can
make with stuff around the house. Like
this one. Crow will be my model for this
one. Just take some candy wrappers and you
tape them to yourself or your jacket or
your dress, if you happen to be a human
like that. And then adorn yourself with
some silly string like.
And then you face the camera. And then you
can go as the floor of a movie theater.
All right, and then you get this one.
Take a milk carton, put a slit or a hole
in the back, cut a hole in the front,
wear it over your head and see, you go as
a missing child. Have you seen me see?
And this one takes a little more
preparation. Take some aluminum
foil. I like to use the Reynolds raft.
And a pie pan. And you cut the center out
of the pie pan. Then you wrap the foil
around your head like
that. I know. I probably sound like a
kazoo, right? A little bit. Anyway,
I am Iron Man.
Anyway, then you get the pie pan right
there. Right down on the desk. Yep, there
you go. Close. It's a good idea to put
this on after you finally get to the party
too. I bet. And then you take the pie pan
and put it around your neck and you go
as Jiffy Pop Popcorn. What do you think,
sir? I saw some hack do that at the funny
bone in St. Louis. Frank, go get your
costume on. The lizard costume?
No, the other one.
Well, Panzer, my invention exchange this
week is another easy to make costume.
Hey, you Copy that, Cheaters? Cheaters?
What? What are you saying that you're the
only one to come up with a Halloween
costume by using stuff found around the
house? I came up with this when you were
back in short pants. Can you guess what I
am? Can you guess? Well, by taking two
lengths of ABS drainage tubing and
fastening them to my arms and then keeping
my feet together real close, I I the
goalie of a foosball team. Huh? You get
it, Frank? Huh? And by wearing this
ordinary everyday fram air filter, I get
to dress up as Lieutenant Commander Jordi
LaForge of TV. Star Trek The Next
Generation starring TV's LeVar Burton.
Kids reading opens up a rainbow of
enchantment and whimsy and wonder and
whiskey. Thank you, Kunta Kinte. Well,
your film this Week. Joel Burns deep in
the fine tradition of Kramer versus
Kramer, Ali versus Norton, Kasparov versus
Karpov. It's Megalon versus Godzilla.
It'll make you laugh, it'll make you cry.
And maybe, just maybe, teach you a little
something about yourself. And kids, don't
forget to read Godzilla versus the
Velveteen Rabbit.
End the first part of 1971. On a
small island near the Aleutians, the
second underground nuclear test took
place. But it wasn't as good as the first
one.
Oh, it blew up. What'd you expect?
Okay, we're impressed.
Wow.
Look. Jacuzz of the gods.
The effects of the explosion were
widespread, even on far away Monster
island in the South Pacific. Whenever they
test nuclear bombs, it's the monsters who
suffer. Yeah, everywhere. War is not good
for monsters and other living things.
Rest the beasts, monsters.
Hey, knock it off. You think decent people
don't work? Stop the madness. Stop Monster
Island. I want to get off. Damn kids,
will you? Loud rock music Ah.
Spiny gnomen.
Uh oh. Godzilla's back. And someone's
got to pay.
He's cheesed. You know, I kind of feel
like this opening segment is a metaphor
for ourselves. Souls heavy.
Wow.
Grand finale. Screamers all.
The credits should be exploding soon.
There they are.
A film by Ingm Bergman we're
now right here in our stage. Topo. Easy.
Oh, oh,
okay. Technologically advanced people,
huh? Give me a break. They can't. They can
make high deficient tv, but they can't
make decent water toys.
I can see. Keep struggling for your life.
Have a try. Yeah, why not? Why not?
I'm high.
He's drowning. Neat. Hey, stole Wayne
Newton's suit. A drink? Yeah, let's do
some shooters.
Hey, is this stuff. 3, 2. The bull.
A quake. No. Quisp.
Oh, the kick on the slacky. Rocks on.
You don't have to put on the red Dr.
Dress. Come back. Great. What am
I supposed to do? I'm on a plastic
porpoise. Help me.
Come on, Flipper, save him.
Hey, the rocket rockets.
Great. Let's put him out of our misery.
Rocks.
Hey, you're in no position to make
demands, kid. What's that?
Oh, trouble.
Dry ice and lots of it.
Keep working those thingamabobs. Wow.
This is what happens when you go in the
water less than a half hour before eating.
Hey, this is better than the Dallas.
Try not to get sucked into the vortex of
hell, Billy. I think Billy's gonna be a
boiling a bag dinner soon.
I guess a rocket is standard picnicking
equipment in Japan, isn't it?
Let's go on a picnic. Let's see, we got
our food, beverages and 50ft of uncoiled
rope.
Billy, this is no time to floss. Come on.
Oh, now they can all die on dry land. Get
off that thing. It's rented. Come on.
Ooh. Oh. Grind the kids knees into the
lava rock while you're at it.
Bubbling, bubbling hot.
Well, note to myself, never vacation on an
active volcano.
Hold me. Hold me.
Oh, no. Darn fool toy. I love that thing
trying to save us.
Never before in the annals of Kiddom had a
toy been sucked into the whirlpool of
death. Here he goes.
Ah, we're in the spin cycle. Yeah, or else
somebody took some hair out of the drain
in the bottom, I think. So that's the
beast. Plunge. Don't care what
you put down there. Well, they don't think
this is going to help the tourist trade at
all. Yeah, I know. Plus, we're in a
recession now. This watery manifestation
of a vengeful, wrathful God couldn't have
come at a worse time.
Pretty sure freshen
up. It's really hot now.
Niagara Falls. Slowly I turned Step
by step.
Really makes you think, don't it? Maybe
not this week. Moses starring
in Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the
River. That's Jerry Lewis. Well, okay.
Good. Breaks your heart, don't it?
Drinks anybody? We're gonna
need a tux pad the size of Tokyo in
the land of Tofu Queen with Polhorn on
the flute.
Well, great. What does it have to do with
us?
Well, I'll never get the deposit back on
that stupid dolphin thrill toy. Someday,
Roxanne, this will all be yours.
I'm filled with shame, you know. I really
am. You imagine how I must feel.
Welcome to Death Valley. The driver is
either gone or he's missing.
Well, let's leave that pain behind, huh?
We're swinging into high. The natural
disaster behind them. They drove off in a
speedy car. In many parts of the vicinity,
it is said many lives have been lost.
According to the National Seismic
Institute, the disturbances were
undoubtedly caused by the nuclear. They
also warned that more tremors are
expected. Incredible, isn't it? What the
hell are they trying to do? Wipe us all
out or something? Yeah, I hate these wacky
morning DJs. They'll kill the whole world
off them when they submerge the land and
drown us all. Damn Japanese buying up
everything. Oh, what's that? Where's those
places? I never heard of them before.
I'll tell you. They were continents that
existed A long time ago. You mean like
ketchup and mustard? One in the Pacific,
one in the Indian Ocean. Then one day
there was a big earthquake and they both
vanished. Mind you, I must say the
majority of historians believe they only
existed in legend. The historians existed
in legend. I wish this music existed in
legend. The condiments. Well, at least
they have Yusef Lateef on the flute here.
Who? Reuben? You? Never mind. Must be a
blue moon out. I think was shot blue for
night. Yeah.
Hey, listen, it would be funny if the
earthquakes destroyed your robot. Yeah,
it'd be funny if the earthquake killed
your family.
He scares.
Hey, look. What? Look at the door.
It's open.
Hello. Oh, my God. The humidifier.
Committed suicide.
Hey, Oscar Wilde.
Hi, Kiva.
Hit him with the humidifier.
I have just been liberated by the power
of this. Yes. Cool.
Got him, Mommy. Got him. Mommy. No.
Mommy. No. Not the kabuki mask. No. You
okay? Huh? Okay? Yes.
Okay. Roxa seems
to be okay. Except he's got a concussion.
Right. I still hate these
stairs. It's such a nuisance. I got
unchanged that. Well, I hope he doesn't
ruin Wayne Newton's jacket.
Damn. Got to find out where he shops.
Whoa. Go, Speed Racer.
Here he goes. Mahigo co mahi go
go ma go, go, go.
He's a demon.
Well, it's a good thing they cleverly hid
that robot.
Well, I really made a mess of this place.
Or was it you? You naughty, naughty robot.
Damn. And the cleaning lady doesn't come
till Thursday.
Well, let's clean up.
I'm going to do everything he does.
Isn't those guys really made a mess of my
room too. Why, yeah,
whatever seems to be stolen. That right?
Still, we better make a thorough check.
Okay, let's start with your larynx, kid.
Well, guys, I guess no matter how hard you
try, there's just no way to make parallel
parking exciting.
Let's see, boys life, Popular science
highlights. My own autopsy report.
Hey, look. I found some funny powder.
That's mine. Just leave it alone. There.
What do you think it could be? Those are
Pop Rocks, you idiot. And it
makes a funny noise.
You know all these screeches are on the
soundtrack album. Wait a minute.
Jazzy. Hey,
it's Pluto.
Embarrassing you, Ting.
Try some.
Whoa. New tame.
Very volatile. Good thing
he had the Fun mobile. Yeah,
looks like a fire you all
to hell.
I just don't get it at all. They're
cigarettes, don't you? Well, they wouldn't
go to this trouble for nothing. They must
have been after something of yours. Got
it. Well, what's it? One of them must
have dropped a button. Now shut up and
finish your Laffy Taffy, kid.
Hey, look. It's the same color as that bit
of sand I found. So it
is. You found some sand? Hey,
sh. It's. It's. God's watching
this, is it? No, I think they got this
shot from an old Jackie Gleason show
leaving my body sort of red. Probably off
their shoes. I found it over near the
Robot. According to
Dr. Helstrom, these bugs will take over
the world.
Hmm.
Ooh, let's see. That's me and
industry creating a better world. Our most
valuable resource. People. He's a maniac.
A maniac. And he's dancing like he's never
danced before. He's a steel town boy on a
Saturday. They've just created Jennifer
Beals. Wow.
Now this controls his kung fu grip.
Hi there. Hi there.
Oh, and sometimes. What? What's all this?
Baby Rider. How's it work?
No. You're a racing driver. Oh, yeah. But
I'm only an avatar. There. I had enough of
water. I'm going to stick to dry land.
You really think it'll go? You bet your
life. Say the secret word and win $100. I
don't know. I do.
Oh, how I loathe him. Test it out. Bye.
Bye. Take care. Don't forget to ride
towards traffic.
Damn stick. Let's see. I'll sell a tnt.
Buy a little bit more of American cant.
Huh? It's the All Idiot Channel.
Oh, come in. Okay.
Hi, it's me again. Hi there. Can I come
in? Oh, nearly finished, eh? Hi.
Ready? Hi. Checking over that sand we
found here. It's from Estrada. 30 miles
below the seabed. Hey, you sure? Yeah.
The only other place you'll find it was on
Easter Island. Hal is reading your lips.
Where's that? It's an uninhabited island
2,000 miles east of Tahiti. Down the bunny
trail. It's mainly famous because of a
very peculiar discovery that was made
there. DD7. Some huge statues. Let's go
there now. Through the miracle of
television. They're said to be over 3
million years old.
Well, that doesn't help one bit. It makes
it worse. I miss
our Sunday drives.
Oh, baby. Oh, when we see
love and find love. Make love, baby white.
There. Thank you.
Great. You meet it at last. Yeah, and he
does parties too. You know what I'll call
him? Jet Jaguar. Jet Jaguar, eh?
Not bad. You're right. It suits him.
That's a great name. Jet Jaguar. What a
stupid name.
I feel good about myself. I like myself.
Uh oh.
Size of TV cameras. Also it has automatic
evasion devices. So it'll always get out
of your way. Hope so.
But as far as I'm concerned, it's got
right of way. You said it my little hard
bodied bachelor friend.
That's our cue to go. Let's get out of
here. I have shamed the family. Get out.
Get out. It. It's unlocked.
Oh wow. Gosh, look at that.
Boy, I never knew that they could see the
ditch the pics.
Hey, what are you two high speed bit
blitters up to anyway? Oh, we're just
finishing our monster drawings. Yeah,
that's right. There. These monster
drawings? Yeah, yeah, that's right. The
movie inspired us to create our own mega
monsters. And mine is the grandest of all.
Well, it sounds pretty neat. Could I check
him out? Oh, well mine needs a little
setup. Let me explain it here. Mine is
green and he stands 18ft tall and yeah,
he has flames shooting out of it. Neat.
Yeah, well mine has flames too. And it's
20ft tall and has a big claw thingy.
Well mine has two claw thingies and he
uses them to eat railroad trains. Oh.
Well mine has a secret that there's
an elf in his head. Elf in his head?
What? An elf? He's got an elf and a
trillion times the atom bound power. Oh,
and it's got a hydraulic tail stomper. Oh
sure. Well mine is a million jillion times
more powerful than that any day of the
week. Oh yeah? Well mine is the number
before infinity. Oh yeah. Well my monster
is a meltdown of all the Tarry Toon
characters. Huh? Well my. My monster is
silent as tomorrow. He kills in the night.
He has been acquainted with the night.
Sounds like your monster reads Frost too.
Yeah, and he sprays it like icy death from
his bloody thumbs. Right. Well mine is
called Gorblat. And he was spawned from a
giant mutant hell beast and comes to earth
every so often to kill. He must drink the
blood of the innocent to live every so
often. Yeah. You know, whenever he needs
to. Well, my monster is a 24 hour wide
awake nightmare. And it has that all that
stuff that I just mentioned. Plus it has
the power to completely kill your monster
10 times over. Oh yeah? Well my monster is
so completely scary that even thinking
about it could kill you. Oh, I bet.
Cannot. Can so not not.
Okay, all right, you win. You win the
world. Your monster monster is the best.
Kills everything. And you're happy and
you're standing There all in your shame.
Are you happy now? Yeah, I am, as a matter
of fact. Listen to you guys. I don't even
want to hear this. You just can go discuss
this as long as you want. I gotta get out
of here. Okay. Phew. That was close.
Wow. I'm glad he's gone. I thought he'd
never go. Yeah. Let's take a look. What'd
you do with us? Right here. Boy, you
really come up with some stupid things.
Sometimes I see death from bloody stumps.
How dumb. Hey, I thought that was pretty
good. No, I don't think so. Yes. I'm
sorry. It was good. No, no, it wasn't
good. Yeah. Ye. Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no,
baby, I'm qu.
Now I can listen to their cable all day.
I think they get the national network.
Seatopia. Seatopia. Seatopia. Seatopia.
Run. Receiving you well, Everything's
going well. Except my hair. We've managed
to occupy the laboratory. And we have the
inventor, too. That's good. One problem,
though. You caught us in the middle of our
production of La Concha Houston.
Hi, I'm Styro.
Oh, grand from Uncle Penn.
Yikes.
Geez, look at the size of that guy's neck.
Wow. Say, these clan meetings have really
lightened up. Very festive.
Yeah, and you know that now that Twilight
Tharp has joined the clan, Anna Kisselgoff
should give him a good review, huh?
I've got a good thing going.
These Bob mackiegons are fabulous.
I'm Dwarf,
and it's the June Taylor lynchers.
All right, everyone, places. Remember,
Ziegfeld's in the house tonight.
Thank you, girls. Oh, people.
Today Ztopia, tomorrow Broadway.
After 3 million years of peace, we finally
have to fight. We don't want to, but the
people of Earth leave us. No joy. The
sanctions are just not working.
They have already destroyed a third of our
country. You just have to take my word for
it. No more Seatopia will strike back for
today. The Earthmen now will have to take
their own. Medicine will harm them.
For I will unleash Megalon to protect our
land, our underwater world.
Great. They're going to take over the
world with interpretive dance.
God of draperies. Megalod,
keep your shirt off. I'm coming. Megalod,
what is this? My wake up call was for
Seven. Come on.
Rise up. Now. To the Earth. Seven. You
destroy the Earth. Destroy our enemies.
Rise up. At least send us a
llama lamp or something. Please.
Go on, Megalod. Come on you,
wolf.
Whoa, Sparky,
watch him me up. This guy does not know
how to make a normal entrance.
If Siegfried and Ryan got a wake up call,
I think it would look something like this.
I would say eye protection should be worn
in this area.
Jules Podel presents Jubilee 90.
Oh boy, do I have a hangover.
Oh, it's Edward Scissorhands.
What a hot head.
Looks kind of like a Christmas tree
monster. Hey, and his arms look like the
Chrysler Building.
Ooh, he awakes with with the worst special
effects of the morning. Well, button up
the sleeve and crystal must be a seven
and a half.
Hey, how about a little applause? I did
this act with David Copperfield in Reno
and got standing O's all week.
Thank you. I'll be in Atlantic City next
week with funny man Jimmy Walker.
Thanks.
Wow. Neat, huh? So it was all a dream,
huh? Wow. Oh,
say. Oh,
excuse me. Huh?
Oh,
if I could only get to my utility belt.
I invented it, you know. Batman stole it
from me. Sour cream.
We've been performing Houdini's
Metamorphosis for years and now we both
end up tied in a box. Ironic. I can see
myself in this floor.
Oh, they're in a fry pan. Metal.
We're in some kind of metal box. Hmm,
good. What are we going to do? I reckon
they mean to kill us. You reckon? Hey,
you're Japanese EB san. Now then,
get busy. Work on this rope. What do you
want? The Kaido.
Now we can watch the Importance of Being
Earnest on video.
This is my Kraft American singles machine.
It's Swiss operation.
The Goofy game for Japanese Oscar Wilde
look alikes.
Oh, do I hate these stairs. I'm a robot
and I hate these stairs. I'll get the
mail.
What a day. I feel grand.
God, I love my job.
Oh great. You tied us together.
Thank you ladies and gentlemen. Thank you
very much. That was surprising. Yu Gi
oh has left the stadium.
Meanwhile, BJ and the Bear go to Japan in
breaking training.
I'm getting red burns on my teeth. You are
right there. I have to go to the bathroom.
Keep going.
Hey, how is all three of them can be
driving? Well, the way I see it, it's none
of our business anyway. I mean we're
getting a hundred thousand yen. Yeah,
real funny. That's like four bucks or now
I'm going to read you parts. A picture of
Dorian Gray. And I want you to be honest
with me.
Thought I'd get a better table than this.
Can't even see the stage.
Well, where are the others now? They're in
the truck. Okay. It said done.
Okay, Gotta go. Call me if you survive,
kid. We're cruising. Cruising at 50,000ft.
Geez, I really gotta go.
Reporting. The robot is at the lake.
All's ready. The inventor
will be there soon. He's on his way now
with a brother. Excellent. A bra. Our
elevator is already moving upwards and
will emerge from a crack in the lake bed.
You've been the raspberry seed in my
wisdom tube for long enough. Where are you
taking my friend? To the kingdom of
Seatopia. That sounds new.
That's right. It's a country below the
surface of the sea. It was engulfed in an
earthquake millions of years ago, and most
of its people survived. They managed to
create their own oxygen supply and later
were able to construct their own sun. So
the legend's true. We're a very advanced
people. Except for our haircuts are much
superior to yours. Well, if you're so damn
clever, why still our robot? That's a good
point. We have few people. We need to have
robots in order to build up an army. And
we don't have the time to invent them.
Oh, yeah? You mean you're too dumb.
Okay, we may be advanced, but we don't
take sarcasm well. I wasn't being
sarcastic. You Jack. All I'm saying is,
if you're going to criticize us, you'll
have to cushion it a bit. Come on. We're
sensitive. Gotta run.
Wrong way. Wrong way. Over here. Oh.
Okay. Good. All these stairs.
Steps are a real pain.
Hey, someone stole the top of his car.
Andy's on the wrong side. All right.
Right. That's got it. Look out.
Watch your hand. Oh. Help me. Why? Still.
Either these drapes go or I do. I'm having
trouble lifting up to my china. Huh?
Oh. Oh, I have
such a beef over Unit
One. Unit One. Unit One here. Come in,
please. My prisoner has just escaped.
He'll try to rescue the inventor of the
robot. He's also aware of the whole story
of our mission here. I got it. Chatty Rex
Dart, Eskimo spy.
Oh, another one. Seen that?
I'm huge.
Hey, I'm feeling pretty good.
Raps Dart pops the clutch and tells the
hogs to eat his dust.
Action sequences filmed in Confuso Vision.
Wow. It sounds like the Allman Brothers
are doing the background. Yeah. In fact,
that's Dwayne Allman on the motorcycle
there. Maybe it's Barry Oakland.
Oh, you'll know my little shortcut.
This is no place for a convertible. You
know, I think Peter Bogdanovich shot this
sequence here. That's why it's so funny.
You know, in France, this scene would be
considered genius. Yeah, I have to
remember that route cuts 15 minutes off my
drive time.
Suddenly we're watching Mannix. You know,
in France, Mike Connors is considered a
genius. Mike Connors is Mannix.
Well, there's a lot of congestion on the
interstate this morning. You might want to
consider taking an alternate route. Say,
down the side of a steep mountain. A man
who drove down Everest.
I haven't seen this much accent since
Herbie Goes to Mexico. You know, in
France, Dean Jones is constant. Shut up.
Yeah.
Whoa. Hey, guys, it's Steve McQueen. You
know, Steve McQueen is considered.
There really is construction.
Eat a peach, dude.
Oh, he's okay.
Gary Busey is back on the bike.
Gary Busey is not considered genius. Oh,
look out, Herbie.
It kooks me out.
Huh? What? GI Better
luck next next time. Kooky. What a mess.
The gods do not approve of this inept car
chase sequence.
All right, forget everything you've seen
until now. That's right.
It's time for the headliner.
For my first trick, I will use an ordinary
metropolitan city. It's great. Change the
channel. I hate it. I'll guide it
to Tokyo immediately. Toky winged
freak. Wait till they get a load of me.
Curse you, Jet Jaguar, and everything you
stand for.
Atomic batteries of power. Turbines to
speed. Ready to go back.
Not pretty, but get me there now.
Why is Pavarotti holding these guys
hostage?
Run, everybody, run. Pink lady and Jeff
are back. Or Pink lady and Depp.
Well, you know, security is tight at these
Japanese rock concerts. Yeah, they're
going all the way to make sure McCartney
doesn't bring any more dope into the
country. You mean Linda? That's probably
it. Look at that. It's amazing what
they're doing with ho scale these days.
It's pretty fakey, isn't it?
Oh, come on, fakie.
Real, real. Hey, I think this is footage
from the war for him. Hey, General, where
are you going? I'm going to Berlin to
personally shoot that paper hanging son of
a bitch. Or not. That was pretty good.
Told you we should have carpooled. No.
Oh, thank you, Flaky. Oh, yeah. You can
see brush strokes. Look. Big hair. Big
hair. Saigon. I can't
believe I'm in a model of Saigon. Now I
sing La Traviata what all
Now. Hey, bud. Huh? Chinese fire drill.
No. Whoa. They're gonna attack the
monster with a fresnel light. I think it's
A baby Junior. Wow.
Hey,
everybody. Come everybody. Hey, the UPS
man is here. I got some bullets on order.
The brown bus.
Grab your ankles.
Shoot phallic symbols. At the ready,
sir. Good morning.
Boy, all this and they still can't get the
Comedy Channel. I'm sorry.
So are they setting all this up to repel
the boy and his brother? Or the monster?
Or maybe us? I don't
know.
Overdam thanks.
Know what? We stop moving. Duh.
Smart kid.
Excuse me. What now? Scream?
Die maybe. Quick, brace your legs.
I guess it was.
Bye bye. Well, it's one of those houses at
the center of the universe where it's all
gravity is all. Weird,
huh? Is that you?
What? Oh, that's really scary, isn't it?
Come on. Oh,
it's just a big roach. Monster.
No. Did someone say monster?
I wed him.
Hey, mister, will you give us a ride,
please? That damn monster. He's here.
Where's the European gun? We threw him out
of the truck. Can I ride
too? The Volkswagen. I'll fit. Here's a
preview of my Broadway show.
Yep, it's make a launch Broadway
Aquitainal 91. I'll be joined by my pals,
Ben Vereen, Hal Linden and Anita Gillette.
Oh. See you later. Bye bye. We got to go
too. Just get out of here.
Stand by for action.
Let's start. Eskimo Spy Rex
Dart. Eskimo Spy Rex
Dart is Eskimo Spy meat.
Huh? Oh, it's movie time. Let's go.
Oh, great.
We see more of that car actually. Yeah.
Rex starts. Cool. Hey,
uh. Oh.
Damn monster. Pop the clutch. Engage the
ignition. Check my blind spot. It's. It's
flooded. Oh, let me go through.
Hey, you gonna buy tickets for the show or
what? I whipped myself again.
Now don't give me any of that crap about
high ticket prices. It's a good show.
Oh, damn. Busted. You think it's cheap
producing an effect like this.
And that's not even counting the cost of
rehearsal space. My accompaniment,
costumes, sets. Thank you, girl.
That's three times. Now it's starting to
sting. Pretty impressive,
huh? Well, that was just the beginning.
Just sharpened these up for a little
truck. Alamo.
Whoa. It's up. It might be.
It could be. It is. It's a home run.
Hey, hey. No. That wasn't that bad.
I've got to call the theater guild. Warn
Nabit. I have seen a
bridge too far. Not for me.
You know, that monster does not know the
meaning of the word around.
Really doesn't this is no
time to sleep, my little fairy princesses.
Roxa. Princes. Roxa. You don't have to
wear that dress tonight, my love.
Goro, darling, you all
right? I'll live. Great.
Where are you hiding?
I'm taunting you, Taunt.
Isn't that Jack Jaguar there? No, it's
another superhero of your own design.
Damn. They're controlling him. It's a pity
we can't send Jack Jaguar to go and get
Godzilla. Man. It's a pity we can't kill
you and get away with it. We'll try. But
how? With this. Your PA
Medallion Control transmitter. In case the
main computer fails. And it goes with my
sweater. Ah. Oh, good. Why not?
This thing can only operate when it's got
line of sight. Umpire, kill
indiscriminately.
Somebody can tell. Raymond Burr. He late.
That tickles. You guys. You guys make me
laugh. Kind of.
Cut it out.
Throwing it all at him. All those toy
guns. Come on, kid. That. Guys, this isn't
funny.
Oh, I'd like to thank the fine people of
Seopia for giving me these totally useless
arms. You are going
to die. You know why? Because I'm going to
kill you. Well, soldiers, was the
fetuccini to your liking? I trust the wine
was palatable. Good. Kill them.
I can't take it. Calgon, take me away.
Oh, that's so cruel. For the rainforest,
man, I tell you.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, making a mess
thing. Burn, burn, burn. Yep,
$5 models there. That was a roll. Just
blew up. Well, it's worth a try.
Maybe. You think he can get Godzilla?
Sure, but still Mickey Mouse.
At the moment he's still controlled by the
computer. I know, but this transmitter
signals will override the computer
controls. I'm skeptical. Sure. Well,
let's give it a try. Right?
I've enjoyed our time together.
Hey, you're listening to laser 104. So
tune it in and rip the knob off.
You quit clowning and try to keep up.
Come with me. You'll be my date.
Hey, look, it's Ugly John.
Incoming wounded. Attention all personnel.
I wonder if McLean Stevenson is on that
chopper. What he's doing on that chopper.
This is the only fun the most of it. This
is great. He gives us all a bad meme.
I've got a date with death. Hey, he.
He's doing the monster mash. You know,
mash with.
Oh, what a rush that is on the screen.
Blew me away. Saturday the 14th. I hate
that movie.
Huh? Oh,
Jaguar, stop. They're playing Chinese
chicken. Or is it Peking Duck? I Can't
stop. What the hell's happened?
He stopped. Get Godzilla. You'll find
him on Monster Island.
Wait, don't you want the address?
It's an emergency. Everyone took it from
street. It's returned to the control of
the Earth people. What is it doing now?
I'm in the shower island to get Godzilla.
I see. Well, stay where you are. Sorry,
sir. Who knows? You might get a chance to
take it under control again. All right.
Contact Star Hunter Universe. M. Say we
need Gigan's help immediately. And reverse
the charge. Notify our people on Easter
Island. Here they are.
There's people on Easter Island?
Whoa. Looks like he's having
one of his episodes again. Yep.
Look at it now. It's all over the place.
Yeah, because it's lost its control. Oh,
we all get like that sometimes. Hey, get
him some lithium. Think so.
Whoa,
whoa. Monster 2.
00. Guys, he's very vulnerable
right now. This is not a good time to
attack him.
Wow. Who's flying that thing? Henry
Kissinger? I think you got him.
Overkill. That's it.
Oh,
damn. Hey,
it's a German air show.
Go. Go ahead. 4o crunch.
Hey, that's good view of the fiery hell
beat.
I won. I won. I'm the best. I like myself.
It's meanwhile
in fashionable Palm Springs.
Wow, it really looks like a busy mall.
River place. Yeah.
Hello there. Anyone here?
Huh? No.
Hey, we were just in this thing. I
recognize all these models. Must have been
evacuated. It sounds paint. So there
it is. That's it. We no choice. We'll just
borrow one. What he say? I hope they got
the right models for it.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Here all
week.
Zoep Stadium.
I've got guests. Oh, I hope I got cookies
or something.
What's that? Dad's trapped in a coal
mine down in Dead Rock Canyon. I
understand.
Huh? Oh, he forgot his semaphore flags.
He said the cheerleader. Okay, look, I've
got a few things to do, but I'll be right
there, okay? You know, you could have
phoned or something. I mean, really, be
reasonable. How am I a person of Jack
Nicholson at a Burger King? Do this.
Okay, here I come. I can fly. I can fly.
I can't fly. Oh, I can swim.
Can he swim? And now Godzilla
will attempt to swim the English Channel.
Good shell Godzilla.
Meanwhile, the Tenderloin of San Francisco
goes the marina. Sorry.
Well, that guy's got the worst breath.
That always happens when you eat Japanese.
Oh, that happens after you eat anybody.
You know, I think lashing out like this is
really a sign of some deeper trouble.
It's really a cry for fault.
I say begone, all you condos. Begone.
Real estate that cost a million dollars an
acre. Begone.
Now you're a suburb. Get me? I paved
paradise and put in a parking lot.
Well, now we know why they're buying all
of our property. And our movie studios.
Monsters, can we talk?
We'll eliminate all the noest strips in
Asia if you'll just stop.
All right, who's next?
Osaka.
Meanwhile, on an episode of Then Came the
Courtship of Bronson's father. Oh, Mr.
Eddie's father. I wish I were you. Well,
hang in there. Come on, kid.
You know what? We're gonna go get you some
pants. Come on,
let's go. Okay. I think he should always
wear protective headgear like that. I like
that. Oh,
what, are they at a Roy Lichtenstein
exhibit all of a sudden? Hey, is there an
ethical question about taking a little kid
on a dangerous mission? Not this kid.
Yeah. I can't bear to see you take these
steps one more time. Meet me at the top.
Yeah.
Gee, I hope this works, or little Billy
will be lunch me.
Oh, darn. These Japanese products again,
huh? Hello, Shell.
Was that an Oscar Wilde reference? No,
that was Shelly Laverne and Shelly.
Oh, that's for Lady Windermere's fan.
And that's for a picture of Dorian Gray.
I'll harm you.
I'm glad I'm not there.
Hey, come on. Kids heal faster. They
forget pain. Get him. The little one.
Come on, Oscar.
I'm really glad I'm not there. And that's
for St. Joan. Oh, no, that was Shawn.
Oh, shoot. Now I'm here.
Oh, those stairs again. I don't. I don't
believe this. It's ridiculous.
Oh, you got him. Yeah, just in time. Want
to help? Not. Fine. The robot's gone for
Godzilla. That's right. We've got air
conditioners hanging from the ceiling.
Amazing. The monster's getting closer. We
better go. What about him? Oh, dress him
up something campy. Really doll him up,
pink belly.
Come on, leave him. Let's go.
Him. Get up. Come on, dummy,
carry. Hey, Joe, I bet that monster
is getting paid scale. Oh, didn't you do
that last week? Oh, I got the wrong script
here,
sir. I. I'm sorry. I can't always.
Stupid C. We are sending you the monster
Gigan as required. Unfortunately, the
color you ordered is out of stock. Hey,
everybody, Tinkerbell's alive. Clap your
hands, everybody.
Diamonds are a girl's best. Ooh. Oh,
it's my new opening. What do you think?
Who is this? Destroy the Love boat.
Kill Gavin McLeod. I hate ships. Oh, and I
hate oil refinery. Too heavy on the 30
weight. Yeah, and I hate the Exxon Valdez.
There it does. Oh, not Epcot Center. What
about Captain Neo? It goes
Universal.
Missed the spot.
You know, Monster Island Milwaukee are a
thousand miles apart. Monster island means
mutated lizards and bugs 400ft tall.
Milwaukee means beer. And a Monster
Island. They don't take any crap. And they
don't take American Express.
Meanwhile, a plastic set somewhere. Get
away from that. Are you sure? Of course.
Look right.
These stairs are really getting annoying.
Oh, that hurts. Find out whether it
contacted Godzilla. Okay. Pump yours. How
rude. Really?
Well, that's odd. He doesn't seem to be
responding to the signals.
Jet Jaguar, come down. You're using
an Oscar Mayer wiener whistle to try to
contact him? He's a queer. Calm down.
Try to catch me. You instill me with free
will. Try to catch me. This damn thing's
useless. No. Doesn't go with your sweater
either. I think I know what must have
happened. He's programmed himself for
survival. Ah. I built that into him.
Yeah. He's on his own. I did it, and I'm
proud. You mean
he'll simply operate on his own from now
on, without further orders from you,
all we can do is wish them our best.
Hi, I'm Crabby. Serve me with drawn
butter.
We'll be circling the monster at 500ft.
In the event of an emergency, oxygen masks
will drop down.
Yeah. Oh.
Hmm. Puny man,
that was funny. Do it again. Do it again.
Huh? How did he
eat Wonder Bread? Guess so. Growing in 12
ways. Making the most of his Wonder Years.
Like you were no bigger than a peanut last
time I saw yet. Oh, that one's
hard on shoes, though. Oh, that one.
All right, bugaboo. That's for the
downtown area.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ooh. Just call me the Orin Man.
Oh, great. He's fighting a monster who
uses props.
Oh,
hey, he likes you. He doesn't do that with
everybody. It's Burt Lancaster and Deborah
Carin. From Here to Eternity. Hold it.
Let me take this off. Wait just a minute.
Oh, darling. Oh,
please. Rat Patrol in color.
Oh. Looks like a couple monsters are
fighting down the road. Look. You sure you
want to go? Could be damn dangerous. Daft
Dangerous? Don't you mean calf?
Treacherous. I dropped that robot myself.
I feel responsible. So he's just like a
sum? That's very touchy. Now stop touching
me.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Helicopter ride. It's the
Cox Mustang comes complete with control
line, fuel engine, glow plug.
Thank you. I suppose now he's gonna turn
into butter. And then they'll eat some
pancakes because he's so hungry. Hey,
what kind of robot gets dizzy? Me, for
one. Oh, he's doing the hinder grinder.
Dirt. Look out. Oh, wow. Whoa.
It's the belly. Whomper K.
Get off of me.
Hawkeye. Trapper. What in the sam hell you
doing out there?
Oh, great. Now we could really use those
steps here. What do you know?
Get your face in the frame. One second.
The chop and the kick and a height. Hey,
that bug's taking quite a slacking.
Thank you. Forearm shiver right there.
I know I should be excited and scared at
all, but I. All I can think of is sweaty
Japanese guys. Me too.
In the rubber suits. He's got a foreign
object. He is a foreign object. Oh, can't
be. But still, I guess he
realized he had to hold the monster
somehow. Huh? So he just programmed
himself in some way to increase his own
size. Oh. Well, that explains it. Huh?
It's the SS Godzilla in the. The wackiest
monster in the navy. Now, come on.
Bend your knees. Relax. Let the boat pull
you out of the water. And keep. Keep the
tips of your skis up. Should have started
them on two. We've seen
this already. Thank you. It looks like
Dumbo gone horribly wrong.
Where the heck is he?
Hmm. Let's see.
I knew you were in there. I knew it all
over. Oh,
well, looks like my job is finally done
here. I can mark
his territory here.
Gotcha. Well, at least he's keeping his
sunny disposition. Come on, come on. Time
for ballroom dance lessons. Come on,
Jaguar. Don't be blue. Gorgon was ugly
too. Yeah. Get going. Again. Huh? Oh,
kind of scuff. Just look. Whose side's he
on? The monsters, of course.
Oh, no. Monster. Etoi.
Two monsters at once. Yowza.
Welcome, friend Vlad Zakin.
Enough beating of the breasts. Let's get
to it. Am I high, or did I just
get nailed by some gargoyle thing there?
And my forearms were hooks? It's a little
nasty. Oh, boy.
Patty cake, patty cake.
I won't dance. Don't ask me, Joel.
Why. Why can't we have really cool arms
like those guys? Oh, I can do that. Can
you? Yeah. Later. That'd be cool.
Yeah.
I'm Charlton Heston for Comtel Ho.
Even I respect you on a professional level
for that one. Good shot.
Let me give you A high one, pal.
You will bow down before me. Jet Jaguar.
Do you expect me to talk? No, Jet Jaguar.
I expect you to die. Very good, guys.
James Bond thing.
Oh man, do we have to watch this? This is
the most disgusting display I've ever
seen. I need a
comfort rest.
Mutant monsters rule deep. We got a split,
boys. Oh, we better go. All right.
Boy, Grandpa, I sure am enjoying this
Godzilla movie. And hey, I sure enjoy
being your grandson. Ah, keep talking,
buddy. You know, I certainly have amassed
a fortune donning dorky bow ties,
weaselly glasses and big boy styled
haircuts. Yeah, sure, whatever you say,
Grandpa. You know, Grandpa, I was looking
through some Italian fashion portfolios
and there's some great new looks out. You
know, maybe we could hire a fashion
consultant. Shut up, you little cretin.
It's my fortune and I'll decide how we
wear our hair. But, but Gramps, what good
is having a bazillion dollar popcorn
empire if no sweet chick will breed with
me? Listen to yourself, buddy. It's part
of the proud popcorn creed to be without
the love of a woman. How can we
concentrate on genetically improving our
popcorn if we have extremely abundant
members of the weaker sex parading up and
down the rows of our High yield Super
Chief Double whammy. Ganga. Ganga. Corn.
Sweet fruit juices. Anointing their
bodies. Come on, how would that look?
Well, I still want one. Oh, buddy, get a
hold of yourself, man. We're scientists.
Yeah, sorry, gramps. Hey, can I ask you a
question? Of course. When will you be
dying, you twisted old ferret? Buddy,
stop tormenting me. I'm your grandfather.
We're of the same blood. We're popcorn.
I'm sorry, Gramps, but I can't stop
thinking of all that money. I'm really
looking forward to the day when you shed
your spotty pock marked mortal coil. I
shed my geeky image, sign on a full time
hairstylist, take dance lessons and
disappear into the night. What? Are you
gonna disappear into the night right now?
If you don't shut up. Don't think I
haven't thought of disowning you. I relish
the thought. Nightly. Nightly, do you hear
me? Nightly. Did I mention the fact that
our new light has won the the calories of
our regular popcorn? What do you care?
You can't afford it. You're flat busted.
But our new popcorn au gratin has real
cheese flavor. Good. You should get used
to it. You're gonna be eating a lot of
cheese. Government cheese. Oh, why do you
always do this? I hate You. I've always
hated you. What happened to my real father
anyway? He's in the poorhouse where I
replace him. Just like I'm going to
replace you if you don't shut up and do as
I say. It's my will. My will, not yours.
I've got the keys to the kingdom. I. Me.
Mine. I'm.
Hey, cut. Cut. Can we cut again? Okay,
listen, what we're gonna need, it's a 30
second spot. And try to mention the
product more. We also got commercial
showing here. Okay,
I thought that was pretty good. You guys
still got popcorn in my mouth. Yeah,
think anybody will buy dysfunctional
popcorn? I don't know. Oh, well,
it's about time. Mr. Mark Spitz. Have a
nice swim. So, gang, what does Godzilla
bring into this fray? He brings the legend
that is Godzilla. Well, he's the
policeman. I don't always approve of his
actions, but I respect him.
It's gonna be a tough one now.
There he is. I have come here to choose
sushi and kick butt. And I'm all out of
sushi. Yep. I know what you're thinking.
Do I fire flames 600ft or only 5?
Shut up. Shut up, shut up.
That's right. Tell you one thing right
now. You're never gonna find me in a sun.
Classic.
Picture me.
You guys,
listen. You don't want to die and I don't
want to have to kill you. Got to watch out
though. That Godzilla does have a glass
jaw. Whoa. Yeah. Take your
time. Thanks, Godzilla.
How do you like that, Val?
Oh, he's not supposed to. A spark like
that. Oh, again. Hey, you know,
this kind of reminds me of when we beat up
Rodan. You know what I mean? The old days.
Hey, they're kicking your butt, pal.
Hey, you smell something? Smells like
lizard. Oh, no. Which one of those
monsters playing a gto?
I like you. I think I'll kill you first.
What are they signing for, the hearing
impaired? It looks that way. This is the
part of the round, people. And the
fighters are feeling each other out.
They're moving in a bit. They're tagging
off. Strategizing. He's using the same
strategy as he did on those buildings in
Tokyo. He'll do that.
Hey, Jet, wipe that smile off your face.
Gentleman, Detroit buzzer. Whoa.
Come on now, let's kick some booty. Yeah.
The marines are here. Tell it to the
Marines. What, did the tractor bull
get out early? Because I see a couple of
scumbags in front of me. Come on, come on.
Okay, I got a question. Why doesn't he go
straight to the flame, you know, because
the man is a professional. The man is a
real class act, this. First rate.
See what's going to happen here? You see,
if you. If you're a Godzilla, you're
thinking, keep him away from the body,
save the fire. Pace yourself here. You're
hoping that a Jet Jaguar can handle
another mutant hell beast down the lane.
Where is Jet Jaguar these days? Well, you
know, he's a used car salesman. Jaguar
Oldstown. Careful. All those claws are
razor sharp. Godzilla.
Good job. He's got a tree. He's got a
tree. That's not the Godzilla we know.
He's fighting dirty. Hurts,
don't it? Godzilla?
A tree? That's not like you. Why?
Why? Yeah, you're right.
It's not the right club for this hole
anyway. Now let's go in there and win our
way. Yep, that's the G
man we know and love. Looks like Godzilla
lost his head there for a moment. But he's
back and ready to play fair. All right.
He's strutting, he's getting cocky.
Feeling good about himself.
Ooh, look at him go.
Whoa. Look out. It's a live one. I'll get
it. It's a looty bomb.
Oh, I've had words. Come back.
Fight like a man, jelly squirter.
He's rolling. Godzilla is rolling. But
he's up and ready.
Oh, again? That'll never heat. I don't
think so.
Yes. Somebody get me a tree.
Oh. Oh. And it hasn't even had time to
scab over. Poor guy.
Oh, you gotta know what Godzilla's
thinking. He's saying, knock me over three
times, shame on you. You knock me over
four times, shame on me. Oh, right into
the condo with. That's not supposed to
happen. Wait a minute.
Nope. Now, back to the action. Ah, little
break. Here,
Listen. That's from Godzilla. And that's
from the fine people of Tokyo. Come on.
This one. This one's for Rocky 5.
I haven't seen it, but I hear it really
sucks. I hate
you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll
kill you. Oh, God. Don't let go.
What have I done?
Come back. I'll bite your legs off.
Ah, you know, we're fast friends. First
appears on me, Godzilla. Say, Godzilla,
your tail got longer. That's not my tail.
Oh, great. You know, it's quiet.
Too quiet.
Knock him right off. What gives?
He's insane.
I am going to kick your scrawny little. I
am just gonna hit you so Hard that. Oh,
whoa. Walk right into that one. Yep. Lame
myself. Oh, man. You know, those Chrysler
buildings really pack a wallop. Yeah,
they certainly do. Okay, It's a test of
nerve. Now, people, this is what it all
comes down to. It's a little game of life
called character. Even if Godzilla loses,
he still aces in my book. Absolutely.
Oh, I am going to give you
such a pinch.
So, had enough, little man?
Squeaky justice.
That's a dirty pool. Uh oh.
By the neck. Come on, Megalon, you don't
want to do that, man. I'm here. I'm here.
Take me. Hey, I'm just crazy enough to do
it. Come on. Punk's not worth killing.
Are with you, man.
Come on, Jet. Get up, fam. Go on without
me. We're getting out of here together,
man, or not at all.
Watch out for those spitballs. They're.
Hell, they are.
Hey, those things are coming in a little
too close for comfort. Whoa. Come on,
buddy. Let's go home. I'm gonna get you
out. Na na na na na na na.
Your father was a lizard. Your mother was
an ave ounce. Find it,
buddy. Find you knuckles around.
Ooh. Oops. Snapped your spine.
Sorry. I work them to find us together
like this. In each other's arms, man.
I guess I'll see you in hell, man.
Fight. Fight. You never walked away from
anything in your life. Now live. Live,
damn it. Listen, if we ever get out of
this alive, we'll be married.
Oh, no. Game over,
man. Game over. Guess we'll see you on the
other side, dude. You know, one day,
Johnny Cash will write a song about that.
Although you ring of. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Ow. Oh. Ow. Oh. Oh. It's all
hot and it hurts.
You know what's funny? I always thought
I'd die in a bar.
What? No, it's curtains. What's that,
man? I hear music. Are we in
heaven? No, no, you're all right. Don't
look at the ark, Marion. Don't look at the
ark. Don't look at it. Whatever you do,
don't look at it. Listen, next time you
say we go to Bolivia, we go to Bolivar.
Hey, I got a crazy idea, man. It's crazy,
but it just might work. There we go.
Hey, stay cool, man. Stay cool.
So you want to play with fire, huh?
Stop the noise. Stop the noise of the
metals.
Pulling out his secret weapon, he fell him
like a mighty oak. He prepared to close
all the exits. What do we got? The spider
kiss all of a sudden. Wow. To all unit.
Hurry.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, it's not going
to be that easy. You see,
O.
Oh no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Don't pass out on me
now. No, no, no.
That's gotta hurt. Now we're in the wrong
place. Our monsters are flame broiled,
not fried folks. Kick me in the cajones,
will ya? I'll teach you a thing of donkey.
Let's eat. I see a
loogie. Hey, how about a
nice Hawaiian punch? Sure.
Say uncle. Say uncle. Come on, come on,
come on. Get up there, stupid. Oh,
oh, what's this, what's this? He's going
for the clean and jerk. He's gotta hold
him up there for three seconds and.
Oh.
Woohoo. Good shot.
I thought he might leave.
Enough.
What's this?
All right, who do you work for? Man, who?
Oh, that's rich. Wait, wait, I'll do
it again. Look, I can do it even better
this time. Okay, okay, wait, wait, wait.
This is great. Just gonna do the same
thing over again, aren't they?
Yep, yep. We've seen it already. Thank
you. It was funny the first time I
cracked myself up.
There's a little something I call the
Linda Blair.
Would they call that getting a little
piece of tail? Someone might.
I can't believe it. Wally Carbo. Godzilla
is either breaking the law of physics or
he's throwing around an empty rubber suit.
You know, and I can't believe that they're
playing the Ellie May Goes to the Cement
Pond music in the background.
You got to give me credit on that one
fellow,
huh?
Do you see what I just saw?
Oh, somebody cut the tofu. Close down all
the exit points. Mrs. Higgins.
Hey, he could have just closed them.
Blowing it up is okay too. It's extreme.
So you see that, son? Never try that.
Hmm, Must have closed all the exit points.
Yep.
No Japanese actors in rubber suits were
killed during the making of this film.
Well, let's go home. Our work here is
done. The world can breathe a little
easier. My soul is soaring. You know, in a
hundred years I just might get to like
you. Isn't that from Killdozer? Yep.
Oh,
I just wanted to say. Never mind. Been a
good friend. What's next for you? Oh, I
thought I'd travel around, see the
country. Well, don't take any wooden
apartment buildings. Hey, say hi to Tammy
and the kids. And if you're ever in the
South Pacific, look me up. And I mean
that. What a great guy. I'm gonna
miss him.
Bye. Bye. Shut up,
little twerp. Attendant. Bye.
Bye. Thanks for leveling Our country. We
gotta head over to the house sometime.
Oh, really? Really. We'll rent a front end
loader and. And have some snacks.
Hey, he's never made that sound before.
Must be a rocker arm. Loose. Tap it.
Maybe I'm a belt job.
That was great. Jaguar.
Get Jaguar. Thanks a lot.
I don't have a line.
You're next, puny humans.
He's tiny.
Jeepers. Hey, let's make them real small.
And we can put them in our pockets. It
he's a junior Petite. Geez. Great. At
least now we can carry him in the car.
Yeah,
let's. All that shall eat, huh? I never
liked you, kid. Hey, it's time we
went home again, eh? Hey, it's like we've
never known you. Who are you? Jet Jaguar.
Who the control. Try it.
Oh, this one. Play him a B flat like
that. Jet Jaguar, let's go now.
Yeah, sure. You control me, right? I'll be
home crushing your house. Oh.
You know, it feels really good to finally
have him under our control. Huh?
Hey.
Probably Gonna Go Home by Bobby Short
Album no, no. I guess he decided his job
was done. But still, I reckon he'd
do it again if the need ever arose again.
Well, let's just hope that it doesn't.
We'll warn the scientists to be more
careful in future. And let Seatopia rest
in peace. I'm sure they'll listen.
They're good that way. I'm worried about
that kid. Hey. Hey,
Tech. Hey. I know. Shane. Come back.
Shane. I know how to make myself grow.
Check this out. What you gonna do?
He's making himself grow.
I'm immense. Look at how huge I am. I'm
sure you're bigger than him.
That's really great. And it's the fabulous
Jet Jagar fight song here, guys. I knew
what he was saying.
Wow. Sounds like Jerry Lewis is considered
a genius in Japan too.
The taste sensation of Jet Jaguar. Hey,
get this kid off of me. He's all wet and
he stinks. Smells like ammonia. Let's get
out of here, guys. Better go. Come on.
Please. Come on.
What do you think of these new cool limbs
I gave you guys, huh? Just what you asked
for. Well, this is not what I had in mind
at all. A bent coat hanger. And what's
this thing over here? A lobster claw?
What's that supposed to do? Well, Crow,
that's for the seafood lover in you.
Sort of a long way to go for a lame joke.
Looks like I got the load into the pan
that time. Ah, sour grapes, Crow. Sour
grapes. Look at me. I'm sporting a
flamethrower here. Look, light that up,
will you, Joel? There we go. Flame on.
I am the God of hellfire. Okay,
why don't you let it out? Try give it up.
Give a little there. Thank you. And look
over here on the right. I got a Swiss army
knife. Does that knife have a wire cutter?
Yeah, it sure does, Crabby. Well, snip off
a little bit of this thing, would you?
Okay, you guys, we have to find a way of
Segwaying out of this into that little
film thing we made. You want to do
it, Clay? I'm bitter, Tom. Well, I'll set
up the clip for us, Arsenio. I mean,
Joel. Well, for all of you folks who do
not speak Japanese, we've translated the
Jet Jagar fight song so that you can sing
along. I'd tell you to follow the bouncing
ball, but we don't have one. Roll that
puppy. Kambo on.
What manner of bot are you who can conjure
flame without flint or Tinder? Hey, guys,
come on. We're gonna do letters now. Put
me out, will you, Joel? Johnny Human
Torch. That's kind of. Well,
yeah. Okay. A little dicey, I'd say.
Okay. Got some letters here. Let's check
them out. Cool. This one's from J. Bob
Hacker. Ah, J Bob. J Bob Hacker. Let's put
that on. Still store there, Cambot. This
says, we of the planet halogen find MST.
Very cool. Also, it is a religious
experience. 3 million years ago, when our
race crawled out of the primordial cheese,
the sea God, a vagoda, told of one who
would come. And I quote from the orb of Ho
Ho's hot dogs and mtv. Clad in a jumpsuit
of red and flanked by two men of metal.
His coming will be heralded by the birth
of the Swedish supergroup abba. Enough
said. Somebody doesn't have a life of
their own. It sounds like it says, P.S.
crow must have my baby. I can't.
I don't have a womb. Anyway,
here's another one. This one's by
Charlotte. She's age 7. Let's put that on.
Still store says, dear to M.
Servo. I like your act. Do you like your
act? Oh, thank you. Well, I like your act,
too, honey. Keep it up. She says, do you
like your act? Oh, I love my act. Can't
you tell? Which act would that be? It's
the Mystery Science Theater 3000
Information Club, Post Office Box 5000,
325, Hopkins, Minnesota. The zip is five
five, three. Four, three. It's been a big
day, hasn't it? Sure has. What do you
think, sirs? Hey, what is it? That goomba
just ate that little Mario guy. That's not
fair. I was getting all it. Well, you can
return to this world. Hold down a and push
start. What does it matter? He's dead.
Dead, I tell you. It's just a game.
Frank. Push the button.